there is nothing
admirable or
glamorous about working too much
overworking yourself to the point that
you lose something
that you cannot gain back or have
difficulty regaining
[Music]
ah
there's nothing admirable or glamorous
about overworking yourself
to the point that you lose something you
can't easily regain
such as time or your health or your
relationships
and that's something that i've been
reflecting on a lot this week because
i felt like i became too focused on work
this week
and i prioritized it you know as
everyone needs to but i prioritized it
to the point that
the time that i did have off i would
just spend thinking about what i needed
to get done
and i was letting
frustrations and
a feeling of powerlessness to overwhelm
me
that i can't control what happens to me
in the future i can't
control what happens to my job or or
anything and and
i need to embrace that and know that i
have today
i can keep working hard and enjoy
what i have and plan for the future but
this present moment is what i have and i
really need to
cherish it and enjoy it and embrace it
and i didn't do that this week
and i recognized that and
i decided to greatly simplify what i was
going to do
for this week's video and do it next
week instead
there was a time in my life where i
would let
work become such an obsession really
that
i would let it compromise my health
and i wouldn't really have a any sort of
clear division between work life
and home life in real life and
working life and it was all a bit of a
mess
and so i'm so grateful that i
got the opportunity to be over here and
to
rebuild and rethink how i look at
um my life reflecting on in my last
video to
not live in the future and
to not be so worried that everything
you've done
and built will somehow disappear that
you
forget to really enjoy the present
that's something that's been on my mind
because as you know a lot of my videos
are inspired
by being in the present and enjoying all
those ordinary beautiful moments
and i know that the reason i make videos
like that are because
they speak to me and they speak to me
because i struggle to do that
i think like all of us do while i am so
grateful for what i have i
i still struggle to remember that every
moment of the day and to not let worries
and fears get the better of me
[Music]
a lot of my motivation for working comes
from wanting to provide
the best life i can to my future
children and that is a lovely
sentiment but i need to remember that
the best life you can give your children
is love and safety
it's as simple as that everything else
is just a compliment
that should be my only goal
to feel safe and to spread love
and to help others feel safe and loved
most of us including myself don't have
the choice
not to work full-time but i think we can
choose to make the time we have free
whether or not it's a substantial amount
of time
um kind of a meaningful and quality
experience
hopefully to reconnect with our loved
ones
and to re-center in my case i
always need to take some time to refocus
and rediscover my spirituality
because in my personal case if i don't
have that
all my perspectives get warped
into just something that does not help
me be my best self
anyway i am very excited about next
week's video
and i appreciate you understanding that
this week
it's a little bit different
i hope we all take time in the next few
days to
rest if we are able to reconnect
with ourselves and others and really
consider our lives
not just from the perspective of today
in this moment
but from our entire lifespan and
seriously consider how do we want to
spend
those precious hours if
you cannot relate to this sort of
struggle
that is okay and that is absolutely a
good thing
but i wanted to share since it is part
of my personal
journey and we all have something we
struggle with
and usually multiple things and this is
mine
and this has always been mine since i
was quite young
and i think it's really important to
recognize it
and embrace that it's part of who you
are
and that with most things we struggle
with there are positives and there are
blessings
wrapped up in it we just need to let the
negative aspects
not take over and not overshadow what we
really want to do
and our personal growth and our love for
ourselves
i hope you all have a lovely week
whenever i feel demotivated i find great
comfort in reading inspiring stories of
change makers
a group called clean c reached out to me
in hopes i could share theirs with you
these bracelets they sent reflect one
kilo of plastic debris
that has been removed from the ocean due
to their efforts to help preserve this
beautiful world
people like them remind me of our duty
to always look outside of ourselves
asking not what we can gain instead what
we can do
to help sending my love
have a wonderful day or night
you